[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is true about elephant tusks?", "correct_answer": "They are highly developed incisors.", "incorrect_answers": ["They are highly developed canine teeth.", "They are not teeth.", "They are not really made of ivory."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Robbies surname in the movie Dirty Dancing?", "correct_answer": "Gould", "incorrect_answers": ["Golf", "Geld", "Garth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This American oil driller, dug the first modern oil well near Titusville, Pennsylvania in 1859.", "correct_answer": "Edwin Drake", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert Kerr", "Frank Phillips", "Edward Doheny"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the average salinity of the Dead Sea?", "correct_answer": "30 %", "incorrect_answers": ["11 %", "49 %", "54 %"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the robot in the 1986 comedy sci-fi film Short Circuit and its 1988 sequel Short Circuit 2?", "correct_answer": "Johnny 5", "incorrect_answers": ["C-3PO", "Apollo 440", "Sentinel 7"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who plays the main character Ben Campbell in the 2008 movie 21?", "correct_answer": "Jim Sturgess", "incorrect_answers": ["Mike Osmosis", "P.J. Lons", "Walter Cooper"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "With a Latin name of Capsicum, this American vegetable has been known to the western hemisphere for a very long time.  According to experts there is evidence it has been consumed since 7500 BC.", "correct_answer": "Chili Pepper", "incorrect_answers": ["Onion", "Parsley", "Pear"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which countrys first president was V\u00e1clav Havel, a writer and dramatist?", "correct_answer": "Czech Republic", "incorrect_answers": ["Hungary", "Poland", "Slovakia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What interesting physical feature does the Nicobar Bulbul, endemic to the Nicobar Islands of India, possess?", "correct_answer": "It has a dark cap on its head.", "incorrect_answers": ["It has a bright red beak.", "Its tail is very long and yellow.", "Its eyes are purple."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what big city is the 2004 action thriller movie Man on Fire set?", "correct_answer": "Mexico City", "incorrect_answers": ["Rio de Janeiro", "Buenos Aires", "Havana"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Charles Darwin and his wife Emma survived the death of this child of theirs.", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Charles Waring Darwin", "Mary Eleanor Darwin", "Anne Elizabeth Darwin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 2006 movie is this quote from: I always wanted to be a surgeon. But the boards would not pass me... So I went into business. But business is so boring.?", "correct_answer": "Hostel", "incorrect_answers": ["Dr. Giggles", "Grindhouse", "Nightmare of Elm Street"]}]